Claire: What are we going to do this weekend?
Joe: Hey.
All: Hey!
Alison: I know, let’s go out for dinner on Saturday.
We can celebrate your birthday, Brett.
Brett: Good idea. Where?
Alison: Let’s try somewhere new, somewhere we haven’t been to before.
Brett: Yeah, that’s a great idea.
Claire: How about that Indian restaurant near the station, Curry Up?
Mmm, good reviews…
Joe: Curry Up?
I’ve been there. It wasn’t very good.
Claire: Really?
OK. Joe says it’s not great.
What about Chinese then?
Somebody told me The Great Wall is very good.
Alison: Yes, I haven’t been there, but people say it’s great.
Joe: The Great Wall?
I’ve been there. I went last week.
It is good, but I don’t really want to go again.
Brett: Well, there’s a new Thai place, Thai-Chi. It opened up really recently.
Joe: Thai Chi?
I’ve been there, too. I went on Wednesday.
Alison: Well, I don’t know.
Have you been to … Mexican Wave?
Joe: Mexican Wave?
Yes, I have.
Alison: When did you go there?
Joe: Last month.
I went for dinner with people from work.
Alison: The Acropolis? That Greek place?
Brett: I’m sure Joe’s been there!
Joe: No, I haven’t.
But it closed a few months ago.
Brett: Oh, this is ridiculous!
Alison: OK, Joe, here’s the answer.
You cook dinner for us!
Joe: OK, sure.
Come on. I can cook.
Claire: Yeah – with a microwave.